click-now.net 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy only applies to click-now.net/click-now.org web site. It does not apply to other sites to which we link.

Your privacy is important to us. click-now.net/click-now.org service is free for all to use, and prior registration is not needed for use of click-now.net service.

We do use IP addresses to help understand how people are using our site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information; they provide aggregate information such as how many people may have visited a certain page on our site.

We keep a mailing list. We keep that mailing list confidential. If you contact us, you'll end up on our list - please send an email to unsubscribeatclick-now.net(replace at with @) using the email account that receives the newsletter/email.

click-now.net may use cookies to enhance your surfing experience, but cookies will not be used under any circumstances to personally identify you without your prior consent. If the user decides to participate in the forum, with user's consent, a cookie will be issued to keep track of the username and password for the period of 1 year.

We will not sell, share, or rent this information. We may, from time to time, use this information to contact you - although this will happen infrequently - or to respond to questions or comments that you send us.

Third Party Advertising  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

If you have any questions, suggestions or -why not?- complains about our Privacy Policy please contact us immediately!
